[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Why did you feel differently about your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "I think because he -- he tried.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "I can't believe that they gave me stick for writing a book that's the truth and I stopped before the verdict.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Should a network, NBC, or anybody else, be airing this documentary, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Is there a part of you, Jermaine or your family, curious to hear what he has to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jermaine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"]}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "So what's going to come out of his mouth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "We asked NBC to comment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "In that moment, what did you all feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "What I was feeling, I felt the same, because this is just a process we're going through.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "How did you -- how did you react to that when you knew that was happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I felt for my mother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Had you ever heard Michael like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Never heard him like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Had any of the family ever heard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Never, ever, ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Well, what did you think they were?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "He was probably going to use it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Why would anyone tape him like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Because he's a liar.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Was Ben not available?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Ben wasn't -- no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Where do you think things are from the White House point of view as we sit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I think we are headed for a very close, hard-fought election, and the thing is I would have said the same thing to you about how close this election would be the week that bin Laden was killed and we're creating 200,000 jobs a month as I would say now when we're having a little bit tougher of an economic situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Or is he just quite cool under pressure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, he is quite cool under pressure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "And how much do you guys have to take it on the chin now for the actions that you've taken?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, I think it's important to understand the mess this president inherited, to understand we didn't get into the mess overnight, we're not going to get out of it overnight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Is it helpful to have a former Democrat president who's so popular out there giving his version of how to get America back to work, or would you rather he just kept it quiet a bit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "No --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Do it privately to the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, he does it privately and publicly, and it's helpful in both cases.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "JJR", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "And conversely, if they go up from where we are now, if they go much higher than, say, 9.5 percent or something, that you'd be in real trouble?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, they say the economy is all -- the better the economy is, the better it is for the incumbent president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["9.5 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What do you make of their battle so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, I think it speaks to real uncertainty on their side about who the right candidate is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "And what do you think of the prospect potentially of a black American against a black American in an American presidential race, which has never happened before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I'm not an expert on Republican primary politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Romney"], "LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "What does the president think of Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Well, I think, you know, he's always appreciated Mitt Romney's -- Governor Romney's leadership in passing his health care bill in Massachusetts.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Where do you think you have been least successful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "JJS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Well, I think -- you know, this president came to Washington wanting to change politics here and change the political tone and bring people together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["G.M."]}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", ":", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", ",", "''", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "What are the kind of words you would like to see as a cornerstone of the next campaign which have perhaps a better chance of overall success?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Yes, someone jokingly said to us the other day that our bumper sticker should be: \"Bin Laden's dead, G.M.'s alive,\" which I think that would be a great bumper sticker and maybe the campaign would sell t-shirts to that effect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NNPS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "But will it come down to basically -- \"I will get America back to work\" as an election pledge, a look in his eyes and either believe him or believe his opponent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "TO", "RB", ":", "``", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "''", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "That's a part of it, but it's more than just the Americans who aren't working.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Did you feel that when you finished it, that you -- when you closed the book and thought, that's my life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"], "PERSON": ["Donald Trump", "Bill Clinton"]}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Because I just thought of you as this funny guy who does Donald Trump and Bill Clinton on \"Saturday Night Live.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "What -- what's that done to your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Well, it's -- that's a lot -- that's a lot of -- that's a lot to think about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "I spent most of my life, I guess, recovering from moments like that, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "And it went on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 454, "question": "It does happen, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Do you have any theories yourself about why your mother --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "She'd been abused?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I think she was abused.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "CC", ":", "CC", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "As you got older, what was your relationship with your mother like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Well, I -- I called her and said I'm -- I'm in therapy for trauma and child abuse and -- and worse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"]}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 466, "question": "What age were you then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I was already on \"Saturday Night Live.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Did you have any more contact with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Not until her death bed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "And how did that make you feel, when she died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I felt nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "I was very moved by my father, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Well, it's not surprising to me that you're so emotional about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Why did you feel differently about your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "I think because he -- he tried.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Can I have a nap -- a tissue or something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Yes, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Was he aware of what your mother was doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ":", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "EX", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "He was apologetic for his own negligence toward you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "For not -- for not being there as good as he wanted to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Which was your favorite?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I guess Clinton is the one that -- that you get the most mileage out of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Where?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Oh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "-- colonoscopy?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "No, just right before it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "So you -- you do it, you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Once in a while.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "My favorite was Donald Trump.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 588, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I think we should play you something now, got a tribute to you --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "What do you make of his impression?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Well, he's been amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Where go you get the ability to do impressions from, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "I guess from my mom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Really good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Who would she do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Coaches, teachers, people in the neighborhood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Anyone -- anyone that she picked up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "She was -- yes, pretty incredible and --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "And would make you laugh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "It just would change her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Have you been able to forgive her in your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "Well, I was going to ask you, were you ever high when you were on the air?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "You were never tempted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Are you clean now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "You don't drink or take drugs at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "Well, I haven't done as well as I wanted to with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Are you happier than you've been before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "AMMOND: I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Do you think your \"Saturday Night Live\" costars will be shocked by this book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Did they know about your mother and stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "How bad was the incident?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "It was pretty damned bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "From the studio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "Actually from -- I think that on the book it says the offices, I was taken to the office -- this actually was a clinic underneath the theater, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "ORGAN: How could this have been going on with this guy, who just seems like he's the happiest, funniest guy you'd ever meet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ",", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "It did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "``", "JJ", "PRP", "EX", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 734, "question": "What are you doing, career-wise, now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Well, I'm doing \"Are We There Yet?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Truman Capote"]}, "docId": "111109pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "What ambitions do you have professionally and personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "I just want to play Truman Capote on Broadway.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]